Yash Urade

SUMMARY

This is Yash Urade looking for an internship in Cyber Security field. I am pursuing my master's in CS at CSU East bay college. I have one year of experience in Cyber Security Field. I am passionate about Cyber Security and Devops. I have a hacker rank on Hack the box and rooted 30 boxes.

Work Experience

Security Analyst at Argus System, Pune

Oct 2020 - Oct 2021

- Worked as a Cyber-Security Analyst, performing various Vulnerability Assessments and Penetration Testing (VAPT) for the customer depending on their requirements. Writing Vulnerability reports for organizations. Conducting internal testing of Active Directory for the organization. Performing VAPT for android and web applications.

Intern at Hackedemist, Pune

June 2017 - June 2019

 Joined as a Intern in june 2017, Developing and worked on many different types of Technology such as IOT, AWS, Android app development and Web Development.

Projects

Full Stack Ecommerce website

Developing a full stack MERN website

AWS Serverless website

Designed static serverless website using AWS Lambda and S3 bucket

IOT project

Simple IOT project for testing the MQTT protocol for sending temperature and humidity numbers using python and Rasberry pi

Android App Maidforhelp

Developed an android app Maid hiring app using Firebase and Java.

EDUCATION

2022 - present	Master's in Computer Science at CSU East Bay	(GPA: NA)
2016 - 2020	Bachelor's Degree at MIT College of Engineering Pune	(GPA: 7.7/10.0)
2016	Class 12th Maharashtra State Board	(77/100)
2014	Class 10th Maharashtra State Board	(84/100)

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified Network Security Specialist from International Cybersecurity Institute (ICSI).
- Advanced Penetration Tester from Cybrary

SKILLS

Hacking Tools Burp Suite, Metasploit ,Nmap ,etc

Proficient languages - Java and C++

Web Development skills React, Nodejs, Mongodb, Mysql, Html, Javascript

OS Windows,Kali linux,Ubuntu

Last updated: October 30, 2022